megaleecher.net 2013-12-05

# Our Privacy Policy | Megaleecher.Net

## You are here

Home » Our Privacy Policy

We can be reached via e-mail at [privacy@megaleecher.net](mailto:privacy@megaleecher.net) For each visitor to our Web page, our Web server automatically logs IP address and stores cookies on visitor computer,We collect aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, information **volunteered** by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations. The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web page, used to notify consumers about updates to our Web site. With respect to cookies: We use cookies to store visitors preferences, record session information, such as items that consumers add to their shopping cart, record user-specific information on what pages users access or visit, record past activity at a site in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site . If you do not want to receive e-mail from us in the future, please let us know by sending us e-mail at the above address. With respect to Ad Servers: To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have relationships with other companies that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. For further information, consult the privacy policies of our advertisers: Google Adsense - <http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html> TribalFusion - <http://www.exponential.com/who-we-are/privacy-policy.jsp> Kontera - <http://www.kontera.com/em-privacy-policy> If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here (http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) (link to the NAI universal user opt-out). We use Mollom anti-spam technology to scan content posted by users, please review there privacy policy from the link below : Mollom's Web service privacy policy - <http://mollom.com/web-service-privacy-policy> For any questions or concern regarding privacy and data usage policy of this website, Pls. email us at the above email address. 

**Updated : 11-10-2012**

Internet: Privacy, Privacy Policy

**This is just one of the many helpful tips we have posted, You can find more stories[here](http://www.megaleecher.net/tracker),   
Do subscribe to updates using your favorite [RSS feed](http://feeds.feedburner.com/TheBestInternetNews) reader or using the secure FeedBurner email update form on top of this post.**
